Nash, Al, Additional Files /4188
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Al Nash Additional Files
1971-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Nash, Abraham (Al)
/4188
3.3 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8036592
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4024: Al Nash Subject Files /4154: Robert Risley Papers /4188 AV: Al Nash Audio-visual material /4217: ILR School Associate Dean's Office Files 5219: Al Nash Collection of Miscellaneous Broadsides 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 04, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Nash, Al; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8036592
- A Tribute to Al Nash, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Organizing: Nuts and Bolts, No. 19 Part 2, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Issues in the Debate: Quality of Work Life, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Handbook of Action Methods for Teachers, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Role of the Business Agent with His Shops, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Union Organizing - Hospital Cases, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Memoirs, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Labor and Politics - Kirkman, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Organizing, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Union Labor Meeting, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1940-1957, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Table of Contents from Teaching Notebooks, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- A Guidebook for Union Organizers, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Law 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Union, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Old Records ILR, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- A. Nash. Masters Thesis: TOC, Ch. I-III, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A. Nash. Masters Thesis: Ch. IV - Bibliography, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cornell ILR - Readings in Labor Education No. 16, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cornell ILR - Readings on Selective Aspects of Collective Bargaining and Costing Out the Contract, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Geoffrey Fox, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- History of Industrial Relations VII. A. Nash, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Union Administration: Duties of Local Union Officials and Membership Participation No. 8, 1967-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Collective Bargaining and Negotiating the Agreement No. 1, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Collective Bargaining and Negotiating the Agreement No. 1, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Readings in Union Organizing No. 20, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Readings in Union Organizing No. 20, 1962, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- A. Nash - Draft of PhD Dissertation: Intro - p. 224, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- A. Nash - Draft of PhD Dissertation: p. 225-418, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A. Nash, PhD Dissertation: Abstract, TOC, Ch. I-VII, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- A. Nash, PhD Dissertation: Ch. VIII-XII, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- A. Nash, PhD Dissertation: Ch. XIII - Bibliography, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Film Lists (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Recruiting (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous (Resume) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Nash - LEAA Passed (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Nash (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Fall '81 Syllabi, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- ILR 120 Sept 1976 Fall (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ILR 301 Spring, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Union Adm., 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Union Administration ILR 301, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  Winter 1975
- Spring 1975 C.B. ILR 300 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Faculty Correspondence Spring '72, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Labor Education ILR 689 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Betty Lall (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Labor Liberal Arts (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Labor College Summer School Leaflets (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 100 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Landrum-Griffin (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Al Nash Articles (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Steward Course - 12 Sessions, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Winter 1976
- Study Skills (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Tuition Refund Programs (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Labor College Residual (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Bibliography - Union Democracy (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Collective Bargaining (ILR 300X), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Fall 1974
- ILR 120 Fall 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Industrial Sociology 120X, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Winter 1974
- Ind. Sociology ILR 121, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Labor History Materials (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Registrar - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILR 100X Fall 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- ILR 100X Spring 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Summer Projects - Credit Program (Box 3, Folder 33)
- ILR 100 Materials (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Gilfillan Inc. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Session 2 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Letters, Speeches (Box 3, Folder 37)
- ILR 100 Spring 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Charts - NYC AFL-CIO CLC (Box 3, Folder 39)
- IAM Chart (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Charts IUE (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Charts Originals (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Communications Empire State (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Conference Part-time Extension Teachers - Specialists in Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  December 1972
- Economic Course - Outlines (Box 3, Folder 45)
- ILR 301X Fall 1973 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Syllabus and Teacher (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Press Releases (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Faculty Corres. Fall '72, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Faculty Corres. Spring '73, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Faculty Corres. Winter '73, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Faculty Corres. Fall '71, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Occasional Paper (Box 3, Folder 53)
- E S Search Committee (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Questionnaire (Survey), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Negotiations - ESC, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- ESC - Assessment of Prior Experience (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Courses Spring '74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- ILR Summer Courses '74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  Ithaca
- Summer 1975 Course Materials (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Grading Criteria (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Graduation Programs, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  September 3, 1973 + September 6, 1979
- Handbook ILR/ C and L (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Proposal - Summer Project - Grant (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Review Committee (Box 3, Folder 65)
- ILR Credit and Certificate Program (Original Documents) (Box 3, Folder 66)
- McKersie (B. Stevens) Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  January 1974
- Labor College Credit Policy (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Library - Empire State College (Box 3, Folder 69)
- McKersie (B. Stevens), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Writing Samples (Box 3, Folder 71)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1972 (History of Ind. Rel. - US) (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Student Publications (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ILR Program (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Labor Program ILR (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Labor Staff ILR (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Student Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ILR - Faculty - Reports (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Labor Division (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Faculty - Vitae (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Paid Leave (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Nash. Communications (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Research Projects. Nash (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Courses Fall '75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- ESC - Learning Contracts (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Publicity (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Nash, Abraham. Vita (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Graduation Exercises (Box 4, Folder 16)
- ILR - Faculty Committee Assoc. Deg. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Evaluation Forms (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Handbook - Student (Box 4, Folder 20)
- ILR Policies (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Steward Course (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Labor Liberal Arts (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Writing in Progress (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Union Administration Student Studies (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Curriculum - General (Box 4, Folder 26)
- NYSSILR-ESC Relations (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Negotiations - ESC, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Steward Class (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Steward Class (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Class, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Steward Course Material (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Labor Handbook of Teaching Materials, No. 25: Trade Union Women (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Labor Handbook of Teaching Materials, No. 26: Reading on Working Women (Box 4, Folder 34)